LAUGHING MAN FANSUBS
Angels and demons were circling over me,
Crossing a brambly path of stars and milky ways.
He who does not perceive his calling,
does not know true happiness.
Watch in awe! Watch in awe!
Flying in glory, Flying in glory
I am calling, calling now.
Spirits rise and falling.
To be with you longer
Calling, calling...
in the depth of longing
To stay myself longer
The flow may swallow you, flying in glory
What are your thoughts on the
International Terrorism Conference?
If I remember correctly, this is the second
time the SAS has attended the conference.
They are the first organisation in the world to build a
Cyborg unit and their technical know-how is well maintained.
Although their "traditions" are
starting to become rather annoying.
True.
What do you want to do?
We don't leave until tomorrow.
Actually, there's a place
I've been planning to go to.
What's this?
An old friend of mine lives here.
This is a Wine Fund.
Wine Fund?
A type of asset management system that
procures and stores wines for their clients.
As the scent and taste of natural
wine is extremely difficult to...
duplicate synthetically,
natural wine tends to be valued by investors.
Since the value of wine depends on its
vintage, it increases over time.
In other words, it is a very solid investment.
Pick me up in two hours.
Until then, you're free to do as you like.
An old friend, I see.
Let's go.
The Truth
Behind An
Unfinished Love Story
We closed just before you got here.
Has it really been two years?
I was quite surprised when you suddenly
withdrew from politics and headed to England.
I have more of an interest in
business than politics now.
I see...
So... What was it you wanted to talk to me about?
You're as impatient as always.
All right, then.
It seems that the upper-level management of my bank
is orchestrating money laundering for the mafia here.
Money laundering?
Do you have definitive proof?
There are files in the administrative
roster that have been cleverly disguised.
It is protected by a strong firewall,
so the contents cannot be confirmed,
but it is most probably a set of shadow ledgers.
The bank takes the mafia's money and
converts it into wine for temporary storage;
the wine is then converted back into currency
after its value increases. Is that their scheme?
Also, there should be a third party that acts as
an intermediary between the bank and the mafia.
But I haven't been able to discover who they are.
If only I could get that evidence,
I would be able to indict all of them.
Please, will you help me?
Who is the middleman?
I want you to help me find that out.
I don't want to feign ignorance and be
an accomplice in this dirty business.
But this is England.
It is entirely outside of my jurisdiction.
One wrong step and it's an act of arrogation.
Furthermore...
You can't act on personal interest.
That was your mantra.
That's right.
I see... Not possible after all, right?
I understand.
Anyway, let's stop talking about this now.
It's been a long time since we last met.
so let's have a lively
conversation about old times.
Er...
I'm sorry, but this establishment
has already closed for the day...
Hey, make sure that nobody else is here.
I wonder what that is...
There shouldn't be anybody here but the security guard.
The noise seems to be coming
from the front entrance.
Whoa... Don't move.
Records of backroom deals are crammed in here...
This will be enough to get me by
after I drop out of the organisation.
How are you getting past the security system?
I took the firewall terminator with
me when I left the organisation.
Good...
Column E-5 has a good vintage.
You, stay and watch the two of them.
Mmm, there they are.
E-2
E-3
E-4
What?! It's not here!
Damn it, why isn't the crucial vintage here?!
A bank robbery, you say?
It's at that branch.
The bank president and the security
guard have been taken hostage.
That poses a problem.
No, rather, it is a blessing in disguise.
As long as we secure the perimeter, they will
undoubtedly hole themselves up in the building.
Prioritise securing the ledgers.
Accident are quite common during assaults.
We cannot avoid casualties.
Understood.
Contact the third precinct immediately.
Huh? The Police?!
Hey, you half-wit.
Huh?
Yeah, you.
Come over here for a second.
What did you say, you old geezer?
What was that sound?!
Status?
Unable to locate target.
Shit. We missed.
Snipers?
Why did the police get here so soon?
You contacted them, didn't you?
You really did it this time...
You cut off all access to the outside yourself.
Data transmission wires have been severed.
Inter-cyberbrain communication jamming is active.
The only possibility that remains is...
that that thing remained active on
the link despite the power shutdown.
But that doesn't feel right...
English banks do not trust
the police in principle.
After all, the security system here
connects to a private security company.
If unauthorized access to the ledgers was detected by the
system, the security company should have got here first.
In any event, it seems that the identity
of the middleman is becoming clearer.
Wine, eh?
Is that a gift for someone?
Well... yes.
Hmm, I'll take this.
What kind of person are you giving the gift to?
I can wrap the present to
suit the person's character.
No, this is just fine.
I never heard anything about the
police being involved in wine dealings.
Stop bluffing!
There was no gunshot when those snipers fired.
The only reason they would be using
silenced weapons is assassination.
You two are in a critical situation.
You can no longer return to the mafia.
Even if you were to surrender to the police,
there's no guarantee you would survive.
Wait!
We have hostages.
Doesn't that mean that they
can't easily make a move?
No, we have no value as hostages.
Does that mean that they are
trying to get rid of us as well?
Most likely.
"Eliminate all who may have
noticed that the ledgers exist."
It's basic cover-up strategy.
Any suspicions regarding the
outcome can easily be dealt with.
I'm affiliated with the Japanese police.
There is a high possibility that my
superior is inside that building.
I request a report on the current situation, disclosure
of pertinent information, and to join the operation.
Refused!
We will deal with activities in our jurisdiction.
Interfere any more and we'll place you in custody!
Times like this remind me of how fortunate
we are to have someone like the Chief,
who can forge a path through any red tape.
You two, show me the weapons
that you've brought with you.
You also have a map, don't you?
I'll formulate a strategy
based on the information.
What did you say?
Don't screw with us, old man!
Remember your place!
Relax.
We don't want to be killed this easily, either.
You offer your weapons. I will offer my wisdom.
We have no time.
Be quick about it.
Even the press are here...
That would be the Major's doing.
This will make it difficult for them to take drastic
actions such as using explosives or snipers.
I've done what you asked, old man.
Now what?
You said you had a hand grenade, right?
What do you want to do with it?
It's not like I trust you yet.
Try something funny and...
We need to buy some time if we're going to escape.
That is their only entrance
in the event of an assault.
We're going to plant a trap.
To your positions, quickly!
The press got here faster
than I thought they would.
As we thought,
it looks like a raid is our only option.
All men are in position!
We have identified two of the individuals
who were recorded by the security cameras.
The rest are considered accomplices.
Remember this well!
Listen up!
If the targets resist, show no mercy!
I shouldn't have to mention that you
will rescue the hostages unharmed!
However, killing or capturing the targets takes priority
over saving the hostages in any extreme circumstances.
Hey, you're about to enter a restricted area.
I have some private business with you, though...
What private business is that?
I did what you asked.
But, it is really all right
to rig a trap like this?
It's fine.
Now what should we do?
Move the unconscious security guard.
It'll be too dangerous to leave him
here when the police raid the building.
How the hell is that old man so
efficient about this type of thing?
How should I know?
After you two are finished,
save the shadow ledger data.
Good.
I've bought us all the time I can.
It's about time we make
preparations to escape as well.
A bomb in the front entrance?
The fools.
I'm changing the entry point!
We'll break in from the apartment next door!
I'll lead the attack.
Prepare for all contingencies!
Commander!
What's wrong?
The wine!
What?!
It seems to be of a fairly good vintage.
Idiots!
Where are the targets?
Commander!
Did you find them?
We've discovered a possible hostage!
He matches the data.
He's a security guard for this bank.
He is unconscious,
but he does not appear to be injured.
A sewer system?
They must have escaped while pretending to resist.
Secure the rear sewer exits!
We will continue to pursuit!
Commander!
Call the bomb disposal squad.
There's a bomb on the hostage.
Damn it, the bomb in the entrance was a decoy!
Those bastards, trying to buy time with tricks...!
Now, how would the Chief escape after this?
Hurry up and disarm the thing!
What is it?
It's just an alarm clock.
It was a decoy?!
What is the status of the other pursuit team?!
Have they secured the targets at the rear exits?!
We have blocked off all routes.
They have nowhere to run!
We have blocked off all the
exits to the sewer system,
but we haven't found them.
They've disappeared into thin air.
Nonsense!
Expand the perimeter and conduct
a thorough search of the sewers.
Find them at all costs, understood?
Where could they have escaped?
Well, well...
What would you have done if I hadn't noticed this?
I knew you'd find it.
My apologies for the delay... but they
took their sweet time clearing out of here.
Or, would you have preferred
me to arrive even later?
In that case, the temperature- and
humidity-sensitive wines would have been sacrificed.
We put quite a few bottles put there, after all.
Hmm... a hidden wine cellar, eh?
It seems the higher-quality wines were
stored in a different location altogether.
Give up on the wine this time around.
If you do, I'll let you go.
Thanks to you, we obtained data
on the shadow ledgers, after all.
Well? To be in such a
situation and still be alive...
Don't you think you should be grateful?
Are you okay with letting them go like that?
Even though it ended as a mere attempt,
they certainly qualify as criminals.
Hmph. Well, it doesn't matter.
After all, it's out of my jurisdiction.
They still cannot find them?!
Did you find them?
Excuse me, sir.
A man named Aramaki is here to see you.
What?
What you see here is documentation of past illegal
dealings; this proves your relationship with the mafia.
It was a well thought-out method of money
laundering that did not leave any traces,
but you should have maintained your
regard for the value of human life.
Where have you been hiding all this time?
"In wine, truth."
That is an English saying, is it not?
I've handed over the data to British Public Safety.
We've provided the catalyst for the investigation.
They will continue the search.
I'm sorry to get you involved
in something so troublesome.
But thanks to you, I was saved.
Thank you.
What?
Eh, me helping you was natural considering the
circumstances; no need for you to concern yourself.
Well then, allow me to excuse myself.
Send your husband my regards.
What? Oh, this.
I intended to keep quiet about this,
but at that time, I never did get married.
The reason I still came here is because
I wanted to stand on my own two feet.
This is just to discourage men.
Hey, can't you delay your
departure by just one day?
No; unfortunately,
I left behind a huge pile of work.
I see... Then,
take this as a thank you for your help.
If possible, I wanted us to
drink it together, but...
Don't worry.
This is from my personal collection.
You know, I wouldn't mind at all if you
happened to delay your return by another day.
Just like wine, some human
relationships require time to ripen.
Don't trouble yourself.
I won't be able to go through customs with this.
Major, have a drink with me
when we get back to the hotel.
Oh, what good timing.
I just bought this this afternoon.
Hmph, I'd expect no less from you.
She's so cold and human
It's something humans do
She stays so cold in her soul, she's so number 9
She's incredible math
Just incredible math
And is she really human?
She says there's something new
But wake a lithium flower, just about to bloom
I smell lithium now
Smelling lithium now
How... is she what she doesn't say
She doesn't say
How is she when she doesn't suffer
I wonder what she does when she wakes up
When she wakes up